running always helped clear my mind I
had no idea what I was about to run into
hello do you like games trucker who are
you this is how the system works Trevor
it's a game called manage your money and
all you have to do is keep things
spinning this is your mortgage you must
keep it spinning at all times this is
your checking account this is your
savings account and your line of credit
your checking accounts running out
better transfer from savings now you're
not earning any interest
look out Trevor your line of credit is
wobbly remember keep that morning
spinning every two weeks this is hard
why is it hard traffic to many parts and
a system fair the game is designed
designed to make you fail would you like
to see a mortgage done differently this
is manual life one your mortgage savings
line of credit and check-in combined in
a single account when you deposit income
you automatically pay down debt which
means you're instantly paying less
interest when you need money you draw
from the same account and so simple to
manage you could save thousands of
dollars by doing less